<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Acolyte_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You have spent your life in service to a temple, learning sacred rites and providing sacrifices to the god or gods you worship. Serving the gods and discovering their sacred works will guide you to greatness.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Religion"&gt;Religion&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you can recite a magical &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_LHB_IB_PrayerOfHealing"&gt;Prayer of Healing&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Charlatan_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You’re an expert in manipulation, prone to exaggeration and more than happy to profit from it. Bending the truth and turning allies against each other will lead to greater success down the road.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Deception"&gt;Deception&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you may &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_LHB_IB_Enthrall"&gt;Enthrall&lt;/LSTag&gt; an enemy once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Criminal_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You have a history of breaking the law and survive by leveraging less-than-legal connections. Profiting from criminal enterprise will lead to greater opportunities in the future.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SleightOfHand"&gt;Sleight of Hand&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you gain a +1 bonus to Initiative Rolls.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Entertainer_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You live to sway and subvert your audience, engaging common crowds and high society alike. Preserving art and bringing joy to the hapless and downtrodden heightens your charismatic aura.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Performance"&gt;Performance&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you may cast a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_LHB_IB_NathairsMischief"&gt;Mischief&lt;/LSTag&gt; spell once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_FolkHero_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You’re the champion of the common people, challenging tyrants and monsters to protect the helpless. Saving innocents in imminent danger will make your legend grow.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Perception"&gt;Perception&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit point&lt;/LSTag&gt; maximum increases by 1 per level.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_GuildArtisan_BackgroundDescription" version="1">Your skill in a particular craft has earned you membership in a mercantile guild, offering privileges and protection while engaging in your art. Repairing and discovering rare crafts will bring new inspiration.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Medicine"&gt;Medicine&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you may perform a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_LHB_IB_GuidingCeremony"&gt;Guiding Ceremony&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Noble_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You were raised in a family among the social elite, accustomed to power and privilege. Accumulating renown, power, and loyalty will raise your status.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Persuasion"&gt;Persuasion&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you may summon a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_LHB_IB_HeroesFeast"&gt;Gentleman's Feast&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Outlander_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You grew up in the wilds, learning to survive far from the comforts of civilization. Surviving unusual hazards of the wild will enhance your prowess and understanding.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Survival"&gt;Survival&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you gain 1.5 meters (5 feet) extra &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement Speed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Sage_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You’re curious and well-read, with an unending thirst for knowledge. Learning about rare lore of the world will inspire you to put this knowledge to greater purpose.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="History"&gt;History&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you may &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_LHB_IB_BorrowedKnowledge"&gt;Recall Knowledge&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Soldier_BackgroundDescription" version="1">You are trained in battlefield tactics and combat, having served in a militia, mercenary company, or officer corps. Show smart tactics and bravery on the battlefield to enhance your prowess.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Athletics"&gt;Athletics&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you gain a +1 bonus to all your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_Urchin_BackgroundDescription" version="1">After surviving a poor and bleak childhood, you know how to make the most out of very little. Using your street smarts bolsters your spirit for the journey ahead.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Stealth"&gt;Stealth&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and you may start a &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Shout_LHB_IB_ExpeditiousRetreat"&gt;Expeditious Retreat&lt;/LSTag&gt; once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="LHB_IB_HauntedOne_BackgroundDescription" version="1">A wicked moment, person, or thing that cannot be slain by sword or spell haunts your mind and flickers in your peripheral vision. You carry it wherever your adventure takes you - or perhaps it carries you.

Your experiences have granted you &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficiency&lt;/LSTag&gt; in &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Intimidation"&gt;Intimidation&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and once per long rest, when you are reduced to 0 &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;Hit Points&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you immediately regain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;Hit Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; equal to your level and are compelled to attack the creature that killed you for 3 turns or until it dies.</content>

	<content contentuid="Shout_LHB_IB_PrayerOfHealing_Name" version="1">Acolyte: Prayer of Healing</content>
	<content contentuid="Shout_LHB_IB_PrayerOfHealing_Description" version="1">Outside of combat, heal all allies within [1].</content>

	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_Enthrall_Name" version="1">Charlatan: Enthrall</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_Enthrall_Description" version="1">Cloud a creature's better judgement, forcing them to ignore their peripheral vision.&lt;Br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This ability will not break &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SNEAKING"&gt;Stealth&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>

	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_NathairsMischief_Name" version="1">Entertainer: Mischief</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_NathairsMischief_Description" version="1">Afflict a creature with chaotic magic, causing them to experience a sudden surge of &lt;LSTag Type="Passive" Tooltip="WildMagic"&gt;Wild Magic&lt;/LSTag&gt;. Wild Magic caused by this Spell is truly random, and can be both positive or negative.</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_NathairsMischief_StatusName" version="1">Entertainer's Mischief</content>
	
	<content contentuid="Shout_LHB_IB_GuidingCeremony_Name" version="1">Guild Artisan: Guiding Ceremony</content>
	<content contentuid="Shout_LHB_IB_GuidingCeremony_Description" version="1">Grant yourself and all allies within [1] a +1d4 bonus to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Ability Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_HeroesFeast_Name" version="1">Noble: Gentleman's Feast</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_HeroesFeast_Description" version="1">Summon a container filled to the brim with &lt;LSTag Tooltip="CampSupplies"&gt;Camp Supplies&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>

	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_BorrowedKnowledge_Name" version="1">Sage: Recall Knowledge</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_BorrowedKnowledge_Description" version="1">Draw on knowledge from your studies to grant yourself or another allied creature &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SkillCheck"&gt;Skill Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_BorrowedKnowledge_StatusName" version="1">Recalled Knowledge</content>
	
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_ExpeditiousRetreat_Name" version="1">Urchin: Expeditious Retreat</content>
	<content contentuid="Target_LHB_IB_ExpeditiousRetreat_Description" version="1">Grant a creature the effects of &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DASH"&gt;Dash&lt;/LSTag&gt; and &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DISENGAGE"&gt;Disengage&lt;/LSTag&gt; for three turns. This ability will not break &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SNEAKING"&gt;Stealth&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
</contentList>